beatscore.com 2015-04-30

# beatScore

BEATSCORE PRIVACY POLICY

This web site beatscore.com (Company Website) is the responsibility of Beatscore, LLC (Company). The following policies apply to Company Website.

1\. Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors  
Company automatically collects and/or tracks certain information such as (1) visitors’ home server domain name, IP address, type of visitor’s computer and browser, browser language, platform type, number of clicks, landing pages and similar information (2) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with Company via e-mail, or post messages to Company's bulletin boards or blogs, (3) information knowingly provided by the visitor in online forms, registration forms, surveys, and contest entries, and (4) user-specific information on what pages visitors access.  
Company may place Internet cookies on visitors’ hard drives. An Internet cookie (a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters) saves the visitor's name, password, user-name, screen preferences, the pages of the Company's Website viewed by the visitor, and the advertisements viewed or clicked by the visitor. When the visitor revisits the Company's Website, Company will recognize the visitor by the Internet cookie and customize the visitor's experience accordingly. Internet cookies are stored on the visitor's hard drive and are not stored, in any form, by the Company. Visitors may decline the Internet cookie by resetting their web browser.

When a visitor performs a search on Company's search engine, Company records information identifying the visitor or linking the visitor to the search performed. As necessary to provide service, Company does record limited information for every search request and uses that information to solve technical problems with the service, to make recommendations for future searches, to optimize search results and to calculate overall usage statistics.

2\. Use of Personal Data Collected  
Company does not use visitors’ information to send commercial messages. Personal data collected by the Company will be used by the Company for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users’ behavior, for product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements, and to customize content and layout of Company's site. Data on visitors’ home servers is aggregated for internal review and then discarded. Names, postal and e-mail addresses, and phone numbers collected may be added to Company's databases and used for future e-mailings regarding site updates, new films, upcoming events, and other information relevant to Company Website. The Company may provide personally identifiable information to its affiliates or agents, i.e. other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing this information on Company’s behalf.

Any personal information or content, including video content, that visitors voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages, within member profiles and the like) becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others. A visitor’s account information (account name, not email) may be displayed to other visitors who may contact each other through messages and comments.

3\. Providing Information To Others.  
Company does not share personally identifiable information of its visitors (such as name or email address) with third parties for their commercial or marketing use without visitors’ consent or without providing visitors with an opportunity to opt-out. Company may use visitors’ email addresses without notice or consent for administrative purposes. Company will notify visitors before posting collected data on Company's Website, or sharing, renting, selling, or otherwise disclosing data to third parties. Any third party to which Company shares, rents, sells, or otherwise discloses personal data will be carefully pre-screened by Company, determined by Company to be reputable, and will use the personal data for marketing products and services which Company determines, in its sole judgment, that visitors might find of interest. Company will disclose to third parties information knowingly and voluntarily disclosed by visitors, information in aggregate form and/or information that is publicly available. Advertisers will receive data when visitors view or click on its advertisements. 

Company may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally identifiable information when it has a good-faith belief that it is required to do so by law, or to enforce Company’s Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate or defend against third party claims or allegations, to assist the court or governmental agencies, to protect the integrity and security of Company Website, and its employees and visitors, and in the event of a merger, sale or bankruptcy or reorganization.

4\. The Right to Decline/Opt-Out   
Visitors may decline/opt out of having their personal information collected by Company, used by Company for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by Company or third parties to send promotional correspondences to the visitor, by contacting Company via postal mail, e-mail, or telephone, or by checking the appropriate box on the online form. 

5\. Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data  
Upon request via postal mail, e-mail, or phone, Company will provide to visitors a summary of any personal information retained by the Company regarding the visitor. Visitors may modify, correct, change, or update their personal record or cause their personal record to be removed from Company's database. Company will only send personal records to the e-mail address on file for the visitor’s name associated with it.

6\. Collection of Personal Data from Children  
Company Website is not directed towards persons under the age of thirteen (children). Company will not knowingly collect or post information from children. Company encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities to make sure children do not access content that is not directed at them. Should Company discover that it had inadvertently collected personal information of children, in the absence of parental consent, it will take appropriate steps to remove such information.

7\. Company's Right to Contact Visitors  
Company reserves the right to contact site visitors for administrative purposes, in response to an inquiry, or pursuant to this privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to Company Website.

8\. Company's Right to Change Privacy Policy  
Company reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy.

9\. International Visitors  
Company Website is hosted in the United States and is directed to visitors from the United States. By using Company Website, any visitor accessing it from outside the United States consents to a transfer of his/her personal information to the United States subject to the laws of the United States. 

10\. How To Contact Us:  
Company can be contacted by mail at 1626 Wilcox Ave Suite 693 Hollywood CA, 90028, California, or by e-mail at contact@beatscore.com.
